we could train
on 10 to
20,000
GPUs. Llama 4,
we could train
on more
than 100,000
GPUs. Llama 5,
we can plan
to scale even
further, there's just
an interesting question
of how far
that goes. It's
totally possible
that at some
point we just
hit a limit,
and just like
previous systems, there's
an asymptote, and
it doesn't keep
on growing.
But it's also
possible that that
limit is not
going to happen
anytime soon, and
that we're going
to be able
to keep on
just building more
clusters and generating
more synthetic
data to train
the systems, and
that they're just
going to keep
on getting more
and more useful
for people for
quite a while
to come.
And it's a
really big
and high-stakes question,
I think, for
the company is
because we're basically
making these bets-
Mm-hmm on how
much infrastructure to
build out for
the future, and
this is hundreds
of billions of
dollars of infrastructure.
So I'm clearly
betting that this
is going to